The weather is so nice today.
Yeah, it's really nice.
Hey, everything is fine
at the hospital now.
I want to go see Pang.
Do you know where he lives?
The leftmost room on the 3rd floor,
404 Changlin Road.
Okay, I'll go find him.
Xiao, the weather is nice today.
Go talk to him.
Cheer him up.
Don't let him look so miserable.
How did he know Pang was crying?
Pang, open the door.
It's me, Xiao Han.
I don't want to live anymore.
Why?
I'm all alone again.
What are you doing?
I don't want to live.
Are you crazy?
I had a very long dream.
I dreamed about
my childhood.
And a girl who was really nice to me.
She risked her life to protect me.
Easy, you're scratching your skin off.
But when I woke up,
I realized it was all fake.
No one in this world loves me at all.
It's all fake.
Warning. Extreme sadness detected.
City's perfection compromised.
Executing emotional purge.
Emotional purge.
Go talk to him.
Cheer him up.
Don't let him look so miserable.
We didn't return to reality at all.
This is still an instance of the system.
And
this instance doesn't allow
any extreme emotions.
Otherwise, it triggers the purge program
and you get wiped out by the system,
just like now.
Is that so?
But there are no missions here.
And no pain to feel.
How great is that?
If this is the reality we want,
why wake up?
Abnormal emotions have disappeared.
Alert canceled.
Hello, Mr. Xiao.
I am the Shepherd.
Please don't be afraid.
In this tailor-made world without pain,
you no longer have to bear
the burden of any emotions.
This is a gift from a friend.
Who is he?
Someone who loves you very much
and wants to protect you.
He only wants you to be happy forever.
Perfect Reality Instance Mission.
Please maintain absolute
happiness and smile
in this painless world
to live a perfect life.
You clear the game
when you completely forget sadness
and learn to be happy
forever.
I received a black envelope last night.
We didn't return to reality at all.
This is still a system instance.